When I was
in fifth grade
I pointed a
gun at a man
and killed him
That's garbage
Villager
you get it too
Give me
the money now
or I'm gonna
kill her next
I swear I'll do it
Sarge
You little…
give it back
you brat，Let go
Let go of my gun
我拉動扳機三下
Ever
since that day
If I saw a gun on
TV or even a picture of one
It would
trigger my PTSD
And send me
into a panic attack
Meds didn't help
Counselling
didn't help
Nothing helped me
get rid of my phobia
我哋好醜
迷わず今
矛盾だらけの世界を
その手で打ち放て
I thought if I
got as far away from home as I could
to this high
school in Tokyo
I'd get
better somehow
But nothing changed
Bang
Looking back
I don't have any
regrets pulling that trigger to protect my mom
But the thing is
I'm not strong
enough to convince myself
It was the
best choice either
Despite being
so screwed up
I did make one
friend in Tokyo
He was the one
who got me into playing Gungail Online
Kyoji Shinkawa
But I've been
totally left behind
That is
so not true
In the
last qualifier
You made it all
the way to the semifinals
remember？
Whatever
An AGI build only
gets you so far in GGO
A good gun
helps too
I spent points
on the wrong stat
Don't get so down
about that stuff
Sign up for BOP
and see what happens
Nah
no point
I just die
Uh oh，it's late
Sorry
I have to
get going now
Thanks for the tea
and thanks
I mean thank you
for saving me
You were
pretty cool
I wish I could
always be there to protect you
Hey，uh
if you want
I can walk you
home every day
I mean
if you want
Oh，no，no
that's okay
I'll be fine
It's the only way
I'll get stronger
At the time
I was so focused
on taking care of me and getting better
I didn't notice
Kyoji's true feelings for me
In GGO
I became Sina
the sniper
And I made it my
mission to take on the strongest players
Next
激啊…
Maybe I will too
when I kill him
I thought the
stronger Senon got in the game
the stronger I'd
get in the real world
I believed it
with every fibre in me
So I took on all
comers with my Hecky too
You're dead
Yes
it's my
first time
I'm looking for a
place to buy a cheap gun
Oh
and I also need
to find out where the governor's office is
I was on my way
over to sign up for the prelim
s for the third
bullet of bullets tourney
When I met a
player calling herself Kiritto
Turns out
she was a he
and insisted on
using a sword in a game of guns
Boy did he
piss me off
You're kidding？
No way
You're a guy？
With that avatar？
Why you？
Even though he
pissed me off
I could tell he
was fighting his own demons
Just like I was
He won't even
know what hit him
Does he think he
can dodge my bullet？
At this range？
Does he
even want to？
Don't…
don't spar with me
Fight me
come on，fight
or maybe you
think I'm not worth the effort
You got it
all wrong
All I want is to
compete in the final
There's no reason
to fight anymore
Then go on and
shoot yourself and get it over with
To you it's
just a game
just one
stupid match
That's all
it is to you
is that it？
A game？
Well just 'cause
you feel that way doesn't mean I do
Senon
give me a chance
to make it right with you
Let me give you
the fight I promised
Okay，get set
No way
That's impossible
You knew
where I was aiming
But how？
How'd you know I
was going for your leg？
I knew 'cause I
could see your eye
through the
lens of your scope
That's how he
predicted my bullet's path？
That's amazing
That kind of
power is way beyond any VR game
If you're so
strong you can do that
Why'd you look
so afraid before？
You're wrong
it's not strength
All it is
is a skill
No， it's not
Technique isn't
enough to cut a bullet from my ikatii in half
You and I
both know that
It takes strength
and all I wanna
know is how to get it
It's what I…
It's what I'm
here to figure out
Listen
Could you shoot
a player in here？
If you knew in
the real world
that player
would die from it？
And what if you
had to kill that player？
Cause if
you didn't
you or someone
you love would die instead
If you had
that power
could you still
pull that trigger？
When death gun
drew down on me
all the hope I'd
put into Senon's strength
was shattered
What time？54？
Black Star？
It's the gun
Why…
why here？
Why does he
have that gun？
Okay，then
who's next？
I got a
feeling that
right now in
the real world
Death Gun's
partner's in your place
He's watching
the livestream
waiting for when
you get shot by that gun
It's just a hunch
No，no
not that
Oh God
Until Death
Gun shoots you
the guy in your
place isn't gonna do anything
okay？
That's the rule
they set up for themselves
But if you log
out now and wake up with his partner there
he'll kill you
Tell me you
got a plan
We're going to
take out Death Gun
Please， Hecate
I'm weak
and I need
your strength
The strength to
stand up for myself
and move on
Concentrate
Home in on his
drive to kill
家姐啊
Damn it
he's tough
If I can
slow him down
one second'
s all I need
Right now
Kiddito's trying
to get that closure he was talking about
He's confronting
his demons from SAO by ta
king on the
person who represents them
Death Gun
And the
reason he can
isn't 'cause
he's strong
It's 'cause he
accepts what he did
even though it
still tears him up
and he's still
trying to move on despite it
I gotta do
something
think
Kaito
Sedna's distracting him with her bullet line
She's got him
in her sights
Using all her skill and spirit to keep it trained on him
It's like a
phantom bullet
One last attack
我唔可以錯失呢個機會
Fool
It's not over yet
You can't stop me
He'll find you
and he'll…
No，Saza
you're done
and we'll find
your partner too
You won't kill
anyone anymore
Laughing
Coffin's dead
It's over
Yeah
My name is Shino
Shino Asura
Guess now we should probably get this journey over with
huh？
Yeah
we should
There
我愛你，阿爾塞娜，我愛
I couldn't have
been more wrong
Run，Sena
But hey，whoa
I realised Sena
and Shino were the same
They were me
我知我唔會過得去好過夜
會係一段長時間
我先可以適應我所做嘅記憶
即使係，慢慢，我會好過
好過
This world…
isn't that
scary anymore
It's pretty nice
actually
Next time
The Queen
of the Lake